Whether you're 16 or 40
不论你是16岁或是40岁
Coming out is never easy
出柜从不是一件简单的事情
There's never a right time to come out as the only perfect time is
不存在一个正确的时间出柜
When you feel safe and comfortable with your own self
因为唯一的好时机，就是当你对自己感到安全与舒适的时候
Have you figured out that you're a part of the LGBT community
你有没有过意识到自己是性少数群体的一员
but you're not sure how to tell people about it
但是你却不知道该如何跟别人说起这件事
Here are 8 things you need to know before coming out of the closet
下面我们将介绍8件你在出柜之前必须知道的事情
1.出柜不需要一切都完美
It's okay to feel anxious
感到焦虑是很正常的
It's perfectly normal to feel nervous or even anxiety when you think about coming out
当你想要出柜时，感到紧张甚至焦虑是完全正常的
The thought of making the announcement itself is what scares you
一想到要宣布这件事你就害怕
just remember that coming out doesn't have to be a grand event
只要记住，出柜不一定是件大事
Some people may feel empowered by coming out parties and Facebook posts
有些人会觉得举办出柜派对或者在脸书上发帖显得更有力量
but it can be as intimate as you need it to be
但是你想要多私密地出柜就可以多私密
2.你不需要一个人完成
Coming out doesn't have to be something you have to handle on your own
出柜不一定是你必须自己处理的事情
It's perfectly okay to have a friend or a loved one
有一个朋友或者是爱人
someone you've already come out to
一个你已经向他/她出柜的人
to accompany you in situations that may make you especially anxious
陪伴你度过那些会你觉得特别焦虑的时期是很好的
This can include telling your parents
这些焦虑的时期可以包括告诉你的父母
extended family or even a group of friends
告诉大家庭甚至是一帮朋友
3.选择一个合适的时机
When coming out to close friends and family for the first time
当你第一次向亲密的朋友或者家人出柜时
it helps to have their undivided attention
在提出这么重要的事情之前
before bringing up something so important
他们对你全心全意的关注很重要
it's not the best idea to come out during major events
在重大事件时出柜不是一个好主意
like weddings or baby showers
比如婚礼、迎婴聚会
or while the person you're talking to has their minds occupied with other activities
或者跟你说话的人脑子正在想其他事情
It's also probably not a great idea to bring home a brand new partner to shock your parents with
带一个新伴侣回家让你的父母受惊吓可能也不是个好主意
Coming out can be an emotional time for every party evolved
对每一个派对来说，出柜都是一个激动人心的时刻
So it's important to give the person you're talking to attention and private time
所以给予与你对话的人关注和私人时间
to help them internalize what you're telling them
来帮助他们消化你所说的事情是很重要的
Before we continue, we'd like to thank our partner TUSI cosmetics for sponsoring this video
在我们继续之前，我们要感谢我们的合作伙伴图思化妆品对本期视频的赞助
广告时间 可以跳到2.25s看正片
4.不要让自己冒险
There are situations in which coming out can mean jeopardizing your own safety
有些情况出柜会意味着危及你的安全
Remember your safety must always come first if you fear that coming out to someone could harm you in any way
记住，如果你担心出柜会让其他人以任何方式伤害你，你的安全必须总是第一位
Socially or even physically,
无论是在社交上或者身体上
then don't do it!
那就不要出柜！
Unfortunately, there are people that may not be accepting of you coming out
不幸的是，有些人可能不接受你出柜
but that doesn't mean that you have to live the rest of your life in the closet
但是这不意味着你要在深柜之中度过余生
If being openly LGBTQ at home is not a safe option for you
如果在家公开性少数身份对你来说不是一个安全的选择
or even if you feel ostracized or shamed where you live
或者即使你在你居住的地方感到被排斥或羞耻
It's important to look for support and comfort elsewhere
那么在其他地方寻求支持和安慰是很重要的
Search for any LGBTQ friendly community programs or alliances near you
在你周围寻找任何性少数友好的社区项目或联盟
or speak to a counselor to discuss your possible options
或者和顾问讨论你可能的选择
5.摒弃你的任何期待
People's first reactions may not be the ones you wanted or expected
人们的第一反应可能不会是你想要或是期待的
This is a big part of your life that you're opening them up to
这是向他们展示的你人生的很大一部分
and everyone reacts differently to news this big
每个人会对这么大的消息有不同的反应
some people may be completely shocked while others may need some time alone to digest the information
一些人可能会彻底震惊，而另一些人可能需要一些时间来消化信息
Others may have already seen some clues that you were LGBTQ
还有些人可能已经看到一些你是性少数人的迹象
and may tell you that they had a feeling
可能会告诉你他们的感受
Some people may treat the topic very casually
有些人很平常地对待这个话题
as if it was just some cool thing about you that they didn't know
好像这是一些不为他们所知的你身上很酷的东西
whatever their response
不论他们回应什么
try not to judge them and be patient with how they handle your news
尽量不要去评判他们，对他们如何处理你的消息要有耐心
6.一个真正牢固的家庭纽带是不会被性别取向打破的
Don't be so hard on your parents
不要对你的家长太过苛刻
Some parents know their children are queer before they themselves do
有些父母在孩子自己意识到之前就知道他们是同性恋
But other parents may have a different life for their children planned out in their heads
但是其他家长在脑海中可能对孩子有截然不同的规划
In their minds, you're goingt to marry a cisgendered person of the opposite sex
他们认为，你会和一个异性结婚
You're gonna have children naturally
你将自然而然的有个孩子
You would never know the hatefulness and fear of homophobia or transphobia
你永远不会知道对同性恋或变性人的憎恶和恐惧
While the world still has a long way to go in the equality department
然而这个世界在平等方面还有很长的路要走
you parants need help to understand that you are
你的家长需要帮助你了解你是谁
who you've always been
你一直以来是谁
and your life for the most part doesn't have to change
你人生的很大一部分不需要做改变
Be open with them
对他们坦诚一些吧
explain your feelings to them
向他们诉说你的感受
don't be upset if they react with sadness or disappointment
如果他们的回应是悲伤或是失望，不要感到沮丧
Sometimes we get caught up in thinking that it's everyone else's job to try to see things our way
有时候我们会因为认为别人需要从我们角度思考问题而感到困扰
but your parents aren't perfect
但是你的父母也不是完美的
they need help understanding too
他们也需要理解啊
7.做好应对质疑的准备
Be open to questions
乐意应对质疑
Know that people you came out to may ask questions lots and lots of questions
要知道，你的出柜对象可能会问你很多问题
Sometimes they may not always feel appropriate
他们可能会觉得不合时宜
In fact, they might feel tad invasive
实际上，他们还可能觉得有点冒犯
But they're just curious
其实他们只是好奇
They're just trying to gain an understanding of your newly proclaimed identity
他们只是试图理解你的新宣布的身份
Note that while it's important to be open and willing to educate those close to you about yourself
请注意，尽管乐意去向身边人展现你自己是很重要的
You also don't have to feel like you need to explain everything
你并不需要解释所有事情
There are some things you would rather keep private
有些事情你愿意保密
There are others we don't always know the answers to
还有些事情我们也不知道答案是什么
Just be patient
要有耐心
8.出柜无止境
Heterosexual people don't have to walk into a room and shout
异性恋的人不需要在房间里走来走去喊叫着
Hey, I'm straight
嘿！我是直的！
and you shouldn't have to either
你也不需要这样做
We often don't understand how much our sexual and gender identities
我们总是在意识到我们是同性恋之后
play into our everyday lives until we realize we're queer
才感受到性取向在生活中有多么重要
Do you talk about your girlfriend when all the other girls in the room
当屋里的其他女生都在讨论她们男友说了什么玩笑话时
are discussing funny things that their boyfriend said?
你会说起自己的女友吗？
Whether you decide to disclose your LGBTQ identity or not is up to you and your comfort level
你是否决定公开你的LGBTQ身份取决于你自己和你的舒适程度
It might always be a little nerve-racking to let people find out that you're LGBTQ
被别人发现你是性少数群体可能会使人心烦
but it gets easier every time
但是一次一次以后这将变得容易起来
Coming out can be daunting
出柜或许很劝退
and sometimes it feels like there are a hundred reasons why we just shouldn't do it at all
有时候，我们会觉得有一百个理由让我们根本不应该这么做
But once you're ready
但是一旦你准备好了
there are a thousand reasons why coming out can be amazing
将会有一千个理由告诉我们出柜是很不错的
Coming out is never easy
出柜从不是一个简单的事情
The most important part is being confident and true to yourself
最重要的是自信、真实地对待自己
Do you have any coming-out advice that you'd like to give?
你有没有与出柜相关的建议想分享给大家呢？
Let your fellow readers know in the comment section down below
请在下面的评论区告诉你的读者朋友
National Coming Out Day is October 11th
全国出柜日是10月11日
and it's been around since 1988
从1988年就开始了
Thanks for watching
感谢观看